Elsie Clews Parsons Papers 1835-1944 Mss.Ms.Coll.29
American Philosophical Society
- Elsie Clews Parsons Papers II, 1898-1937
  - Misc. Formats, Oversized, 1887-1928; 1 box (Oversize 2)
    - Series I, Professional Correspondence (Oversize 2)
      - -Southwest Society - Membership Card file, 1919-22 (Oversize 2)
    - Series IV, Research Notes and Notebooks (Oversize 2)
      - -Spain - Notebook, 1928 (Oversize 2)
    - Series VII, Ephemera (Oversize 2)
      - -Portfolio, n.d. (Oversize 2)
    - Series VIII, Photographs and Scrapbooks (Oversize 2)
      - -[Scrapbook], [1887-99?] (Oversize 2)